mamashealth.com 2014-11-30

# MamasHealth.com Privacy policy

**MamasHealth, Inc**. is committed to protecting the privacy and security of our Web site visitors and e-mail subscribers. To protect the privacy of visitors and subscribers, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our Home page and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

### Information Collection & Use

MamasHealth, Inc. Web site automatically collects and records the following information about each visitor:

  * Date and time of each visit
  * Domain name and IP address
  * Pages visited
  * Computer platform and Web browser used
  * Search engines and search terms that brought visitors to our site
  * The location of visitor’s Internet service provider (by country and state)

MamasHealth, Inc. does not use any of the above information to identify or track individual visitors. Nor does MamasHealth, Inc. sell or transmit any Web tracking information to other parties or organizations. This information is used internally, in aggregate form, by MamasHealth, Inc. staff in assessing improvements needed for the Web site.

MamasHealth, Inc. also collects information on this Web site when you register for a program, or request a subscription to our e-mail publications. This information can include:

  * Your name
  * Your postal mailing address
  * Your e-mail address
  * Your telephone and fax numbers
  * Demographic information, such as your organization

By filling out the applicable form, you are authorizing us to use that information. MamasHealth, Inc. uses this information to respond to your requests for information, for registration in its programs, and to fulfill requests for our publications. MamasHealth, Inc. also, at your request, may use the information you provide to advise you of information about our programs, newsletters, and other resources.

### How We Protect this Information

When we transfer and receive certain types of sensitive information, we redirect visitors to a secure server and encrypt all information. MamasHealth, Inc. has implemented security measures in place in our physical facilities, which are designed to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of information that we have collected from you on our site.

E-mail and online forms are not secure against interception and senders and recipients cannot expect privacy. Identification of the sender and recipient, and access to content is possible. If you are concerned about transmission of personal, business, or quality improvement information, contact MamasHealth, Inc. at the mailing address, or e-mail address below.

### How You Can Access or Update Your Information

Upon request, we provide site visitors with access to contact information that we maintain about them. Visitors may also have inaccuracies in their contact information corrected by MamasHealth, Inc.. To access or update your contact information, contact MamasHealth, Inc. at the mailing address, or e-mail address below.

### Receiving Communications from Us

MamasHealth, Inc. maintains e-mail lists to keep subscribers informed about quality improvement news, resources, and events. We provide users with the opportunity to opt-in to receive these communications from us at the point where information is requested.

We do not send promotional e-mail to visitors unless we have received their informed consent. Nor do we share the e-mail addresses of our subscribers with anyone outside of MamasHealth, Inc. Subscribers may remove themselves from our e-mail lists at any time by following the instructions in any message.

Visitors who have voluntarily provided us with their postal mailing address or fax number may receive periodic communications from us about quality improvement programs. If you do not wish to receive such communication, contact MamasHealth, Inc. at the mailing address, or e-mail address below.

### Use of Cookies

We use cookies to temporarily store visitor preferences and session information. This information is used to support some necessary site features and to better understand how visitors use our site. We do not retain this information.

### Links to Other Web Sites

MamasHealthcom contains links to other Web sites. MamasHealth, Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these Web sites.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

MamasHealth, Inc. may update or change this Privacy Policy from time to time. These changes may include changes in how we gather information or how we use the information we gather. When we make a significant change to this Privacy Policy, we may contact you; however, you should check this site periodically to be fully aware of the terms of this Privacy Policy.

### Contact Information

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy or feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact MamasHealth, Inc. at the mailing address, or e-mail address below. You may also contact your state or local chapters of the Better Business Bureau, state or local consumer protection office, or The Federal Trade Commission by telephone at 202-FTC-HELP (202-382-4357) or at <http://www.ftc.gov/ftc/complaint.htm>.

MamasHealth, Inc.  
Suite 2170  
281 East Colorado Blvd  
Pasadena, CA 91102-2170  
Privacy@MamasHealth.com

This Privacy Policy last revised on 01/11/11.
